Guide to the Andrew Dickson White papers, 1832-1919.
White, Andrew Dickson papers, 1832-1919
- Series I. Correspondence
  - P.A. Durant, June 17, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Henry W. Sage, June 17, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - William Brown, June 18, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Weekly Ithacan, June 18, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    Newspaper.
  - Sage College Dedication Proceedings, June 17, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Dedication Transcript.
  - Hugh B. Eastburn, June 19, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Gilman, June 19, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Charles J. Powers, June 19, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - William Williams, June 20, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - L.H. Barnum, June 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - George Kinney, June 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - W.L. Klein, June 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Henry B. Knight, June 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - R.S. McLafferty, June 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Undescribed, June 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Julia J. Thomas, June 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - M.E. Wadsworth, June 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Letter. Addressed to Professor Russel
  - Josiah P. Cooke, June 17, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Letter. Addressed to M.C. Tyler; four pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Letter. Addressed to Henry A. Ward; two pages
  - B. Wilder, June 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Chase Brothers & Stone, June 22, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - E.A. Fuertes, June 22, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Letter. Also signed William A. Anthony & John E. Sweet
  - Burt G. Wilder, June 22, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - C.K. Adams, June 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - George S. Blackie, June 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - H.B. Blackwell, June 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - W.A. Hardenbrook, June 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Hunn, Spencer & Co., June 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - H.F. Pease, June 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - J.L. Porter, June 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - George P. Rowell, June 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Moses C. Tyler, June 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Henry A. Ward, June 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Wells College Commencement Program, June 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - J.C. Carmichael, June 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - John Holman, June 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - A. Mahan, June 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - H.H. Tilly, June 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Thomas M. Vincent, June 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Gilman, June 25, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - T.W.; Charles C. Bicknell; Chatfield, June 25, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Letter. Journal of Education
  - Homer B. Sprague, June 25, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 25, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Letter. Addressed to D.C. Gilman
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 25, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Letter. Addressed to William Miller
  - Alonzo B. Cornell, June 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Hunn, Spencer & Co., June 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Hunn, Spencer & Co., June 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - H.F. Pease, June 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - James Rich, June 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Letter. Addressed to Edward P. Evans; four pages
  - J.T. Pickett, June 27, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Postcard.
  - H.W. Sage, June 27, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Yale College Commencement Schedule, June 27, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Edward Clark, June 28, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - S.W. Ford, June 28, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - D. McCarthy, June 28, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - A. Mahan, June 28, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - E.W. Stewart, June 28, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - W.P. Van Ness, June 28, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 28, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Letter. Addressed to D.C. Gilman; four pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 28, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - N.H. Allen, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from Johnson & Son, organ specifications
  - E.P. & E.E. Evans, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - George Kinney, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Frederick Noyes, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Frederick Meyer, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Paper. "Paper on the Measurement of Heights by Meteorological Observations…"; 21 pages
  - Miller & Coates, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - H.A. Newton, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - D.J. Pratt, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - J.V.L. Pruyn, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - George P. Rowell, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Louise St. John, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Henry A. Ward, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 29, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Letter. Addressed to D. McCarthy & Co.; two pages
  - A. Curtis Almy, June 30, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Phillip Brooks, June 30, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Johnson & Son, June 30, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Sylvanus Brown, June 30, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - J.H. Siddons, June 30, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - H.P. Thorne, June 30, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Convocation Program, June 30, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Program. University Convocation, University of the State of New York
  - Hook & Hastings, June 30, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Organ specifications.
  - W.P. Van Ness, June 30, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - C.C. Shackford, June 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Syracuse University Anniversary Program, June 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Henry Simmons Frieze, July 1, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Hook & Hastings, July 1, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Letter. Church Organ Builders
  - George G. Lyon, July 1, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - H.W. Sage, July 1, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Alfred Wilkinson, July 1, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 1, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Letter. Addressed to Prof. Fiske
  - N.H. Allen, July 2, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Charles Babcock, July 2, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Watson Gill, July 2, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - John S. Hart, July 2, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - R.P. Stebbins, July 2, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - A.B. Humphery, July 3, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Letter. Addressed to J.W. Williams
  - Johnson & Son, July 5, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - N.H. Allen, July 5, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from Johnson & Son; two pages
  - J.N. MacMurray, July 5, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - George S. Blackie, July 6, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - S.W. Fowler, July 6, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - D.C. Gilman, July 6, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Allen S. Southworth, July 6, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Letter. American Geographical Society
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 6, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Letter. Addressed to George P. Rowell
  - A.A. Yeomans, July 6, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - A.B. Brown, July 7, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - W.C. Campbell, July 7, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - N. Cropsey, July 7, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - A.B. Humphery, July 7, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - George P. Rowell, July 7, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Robert D. Watts, July 7, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Charles W. Elliot, July 8, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - E.A. Fuertes, July 8, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - H.W. Sage, July 8, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - N.H. Allen, July 9, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - N.H. Allen, July 9, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - H.F. Atkinson, July 9, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - E. Norman Gunnison, July 9, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - A.J. Rogers, July 9, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    Letter. Hubbardston Lumber
  - D. McCarthy, July 10, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - H.W. Sage, July 10, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Hiram Sibley, July 10, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - George Walker, July 10, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 12, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    Letter. Addressed to M.C. Tyler; three pages
  - J. Darrowe, July 11, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - W.E. Arnold, July 12, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - E.N. Gurney, July 12, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Hook & Hastings, July 12, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Julia J. Thomas, July 12, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - H.H. Tilley, July 12, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 10, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    Letter. Addressed to John Stanton Gould; two pages
  - Edward Clark, July 13, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - A. Hyde, July 13, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - George P. Rowell, July 13, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Charles Tucker, July 13, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 13, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    Letter. Addressed to Henry Simmons Frieze; three pages
  - A.S. Hotchkiss, July 13, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Theodore B. Comstock, July 14, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Hunn, Spencer & Co., July 14, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Charles Tucker, July 14, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - M.C. Tyler, July 14, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Wyllys H. Warner, July 14, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Hook & Hastings, July 15, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Charles Babcock, July 15, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Robert Lenox Banks, July 15, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - E.B. Mack, July 15, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Edwin B. Morgan, July 15, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - F.L. Requa, July 15, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    Letter. Care of Bates & Bostwick
  - George P. Rowell, July 15, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Jonathan Terry, July 15, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Burt G. Wilder, July 15, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Henry Wheatland, July 15, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - A.S. Hotchkiss, July 15, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Seth Thomas, July 15, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - N.H. Allen, July 16, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - N.H. Allen, July 16, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Theodore B. Comstock, July 16, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - George F. Flack, July 16, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Henry Simmons Frieze, July 16, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - G.D. Gillepsie, July 16, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - C.M. Goodsell, July 16, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Johnson & Son, July 16, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    Letter. Enclosed: organ specifications; three pages
  - Van Buren, July 16, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Henry A. Ward, July 16, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Roland B. Gelatt, July 17, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Watson Gill, July 17, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - George P. Rowell, July 17, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Homer B. Sprague, July 17, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - The Daily Times, July 17, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    Newspaper Article.
  - N.H. Allen, July 18, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Herbert E. Copeland, July 18, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from Edward Searing
  - S.W. Ford, July 19, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Henry C. Johnson, July 19, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - George Kinney, July 19, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - J.W.V. Macbeth, July 19, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - A.C. Shortridge, July 19, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - M. Blanche Struble, July 19, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Eugene L. Ware, July 19, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - M.D. Conway, July 20, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - George F. Flack, July 20, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Hook & Hastings, July 20, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - J.H. Huntington, July 20, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - J.P. Jones, July 20, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Horatio C. King, July 20, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Alice R. Bradford, July 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Edward Clark, July 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - S.W. Ford, July 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Henry Simmons Frieze, July 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - A.C. Greene, July 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Johnson & Son, July 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - H.V.L. Jones, July 21, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Charles E. Brown, July 22, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - J.O. Cole, July 22, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 22, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    Letter. Addressed to Prof. Frieze
  - Charles Babcock, July 22, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Fisk P. Brewer, July 22, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - James T. Riddle, July 22, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - John Snaith, July 22, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Stetson & Hawkins, July 22, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Frank Warner, July 22, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - N.H. Allen, July 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - J.C. Carmichael, July 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - S. Freedman, July 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Hook & Hastings, July 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - E.H. Palmer, July 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - J.D. Runkle, July 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - C.C. Shackford, July 23, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - I.H. Polhemus, July 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    Letter. Intercollegiate Literary Association contest announcement
  - Edward Danforth, July 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - George F. Flack, July 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Laura A. W. Fowler, July 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - A.M. Kellogg, July 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - J.E. Van Natta, July 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - W.E. Wadsworth, July 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - George Kinney, July 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Horace K. White, July 24, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - N.H. Allen, July 25, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - H.W. Sage, July 25, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Thomas Cushing, July 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Thomas Cushing, July 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Jansen, McClurg & Co., July 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Alfred B. Mason, July 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Electa Milliman, July 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - R. Belle Mosher, July 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Charles Tucker, July 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Earl Warner, July 26, 1875 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Henry B. Ward, July 27, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Hook & Hastings, July 27, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Chauncey L. Knapp, July 27, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - James L. Lobdell, July 27, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - H.W. Sage, July 27, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - H.W. Sage, July 27, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - John Sanith, July 27, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Andrew Dickson White, July 27, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Letter. Addressed to Henry S. Williams, Esq.; two pages
  - George F. Flack, July 28, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - E.A. Fuertes, July 28, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Letter. "Value of Cotract for Water Work of C. University"
  - T.L. Harison, July 28, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Henry Wadsworth Longfellow, July 28, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Charles Babcock, July 29, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - N.H. Allen, July 29, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - F.B. Cornwell, July 29, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Wallace B. Fisher, July 29, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - George G. Percival, July 29, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - M. Blanche Struble, July 29, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Charles Elliot, July 30, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Anna C. Prentiss, July 30, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - E.J. Trimble, July 30, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - W.P. Van Ness, July 30, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Charles Warren, July 30, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Henry J. Hetzel, July 30, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - T.E. Heath, July 30, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Cushing, July 30, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Cushing, July 30, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Herbert E. Copeland, July 30, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from A.H. Weld; two pages
  - Undescribed (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - L.C. Williams, July 31, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - A.T. Van Scoy, July 31, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - P.J. Partenheimer, July 31, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - E.A. Fuertes, July 31, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - George F. Flack, July 31, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - George N. Fitch, July 31, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - William D. Bickham, July 31, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Mary C. Arnold, July 31, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - E.H. Scofield, July 31, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - H.S. Williams, July 31, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Letter. Two pages; incomplete draft
  - Undescribed, July 1875 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Grace Anna Lewis, August 1, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - H.W. Sage, August 1, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Burt G. Wilder, August 1, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Alexander Hyde, August 2, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Henry C. Johnson, August 2, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Jennie M. Lemon, August 2, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - E.C. Pearson, August 2, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - E.D. Robie, August 2, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - William C. Russel, August 2, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - H.W. Sage, August 2, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Brown & Allen, August 3, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - J.M. Brundage, August 3, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Edmund B. Gardener, August 3, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - J.R. Pynchon, August 3, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - George W. Rutledge, August 3, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - B.H. Smith, August 3, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Hook & Hastings, August 3, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Letter. Enclosed: organ specifications
  - Seth Thomas, August 3, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Undescribed, August 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Note. Notes of Chimes at Quarters
  - Edward G. Allen, August 4, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Edward G. Allen, August 4, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Charles Hopkins, August 4, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - H.W. Sage, August 4, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - F.W. Thayer, August 4, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - George H. Walker, August 4, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - J.M. Whiton, August 4, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - W.E. Arnold, August 5, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - W.E. Arnold, August 6, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - W.E. Arnold, August 5, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Bradley, Garretson & Co., August 5, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Charles W. Elliot, August 5, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Hunn, Spencer & Co., August 5, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Johnson & Son, August 5, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - H.W. Sage, August 5, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - C.C. Shackford, August 5, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - J. Lawrence Smith, August 5, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - W.P. Van Ness, August 5, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - W.P. Vaurhess, August 5, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - S.B. Woolworth, August 5, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Ms. M.J. Adams, August 6, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - J. Edward Clarke, August 6, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - James F. Chuck, August 6, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Edwin M. Ellis, August 6, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Dean Sage, August 6, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - W.S. Barclay, August 7, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - William C. Russel, August 7, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Edmund B. Gardener, August 8, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - William C. Russel, August 8, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - S.A. Lee, August 9, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - A. Mahan, August 9, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Alma E. Mitchell, August 9, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - George W. Schuyler, August 9, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - W.D. Wilson, August 9, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - George T. Winton, August 9, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Bostwick & Sisson, August 9, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Brown & Allen, August 9, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Hiram Carson, August 9, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - R.B. Gelatt, August 9, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Hook & Hastings, August 9, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Hiram Carson, August 10, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Thomas Cushing, August 10, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - James L. Lobdell, August 10, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - H.W. Sage, August 10, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - A.C. Shedden, August 10, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Margaretta J. Sinton, August 10, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Charles Babcock, August 11, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Henry B. Blackwell, August 11, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Edward H. Clough, August 11, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - D.H. Halstead, August 11, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - A.C. Stevens, August 11, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - J.C. Tidball, August 11, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Horace K. White, August 11, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Mary C. Arnold, August 12, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - W.E. Arnold, August 12, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter to the Executive Committee of Cornell University
  - D.J. Goodard, August 12, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - James McAlister, August 12, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Emma, August 12, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - John F. Montignani, August 12, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Albert C. Perkins, August 12, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - William C. Russel, August 12, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Theodore B. Comstock, August 13, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - William R. Dimmock, August 13, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Henry Simmons Frieze, August 13, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Hook & Hastings, August 13, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Letter. Enclosed: organ description; three pages
  - A. Mahan, August 13, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Dickson White, August 13, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - American Clock Company, August 14, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Emma R. Hallock, August 14, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - George W. Schuyler, August 15, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Dickson White, August 14, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Letter. Addressed to W. Bright
  - W.D. Wilson, August 14, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - L.S. Newell, August 15, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - S.E. Demarest, August 16, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - J.M. Dougall, August 16, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - H.J. Eastman, August 16, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - J.B. Hagerty, August 16, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - E. Hitchcock, August 16, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Hunn, Spencer & Co., August 16, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - E.H. Smith, August 16, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Horatio Stebbins, August 16, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Eugene L. Wave, August 16, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - J.M. Williams, August 16, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - W.D. Wilson, August 16, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - C.F.P. Bancroft, August 17, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - W.C. Russel, August 17, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - S. Sweitser, August 17, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Treman, King & Co., August 17, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - C.F. Allen, August 18, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - William R. Dimmock, August 18, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Albert C. Perkins, August 18, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - M.J. Sullivan, August 18, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - L.M. Townsend, August 18, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Andrew Dickson White, August 18, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Letter. Addressed to H.S. Frieze; two pages
  - Clara Dickson White, August 18, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Undescribed, August 18, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Letter. Unsigned
  - N.H. Allen, August 19, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - George William Curtis, August 19, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - James Johonnet, August 19, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - J.E. Oliver, August 19, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - William C. Russel, August 19, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - E.A. Sheldon, August 19, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Horace K. White, August 19, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Henry A. Coit, August 20, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - E. Harris, August 20, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - A.J. Rogers, August 20, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Stetson & Hawkins, August 20, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Horace K. White, August 20, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - W.D. Wilson, August 20, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Dean Sage, August 22, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - W.D. Wilson, August 22, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Theodore B. Comstock, August 23, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Herbert E. Copeland, August 23, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - John V. Paine, August 23, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Albert Tottman, August 23, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - V.L. Davey, August 24, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 9)